<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Addis_TourGuide</string>

    <string name="home">Home</string>

    <string name="addis_ababa">Addis Ababa</string>

    <string name="landmarks">Land Marks</string>

    <string name="restaurants">Restaurants</string>

    <string name="historic">Historic Sites</string>

    <string name="events">Events</string>

    <string name="menelik">The Mausoleum of Menelik II</string>

    <string name="meskel">Meskel Square</string>

    <string name="menelik_square">Menelik II Square</string>

    <string name="meyazia">Meyazia 27 Square Monument</string>

    <string name="twedros">Tewodros Square</string>

    <string name="menelik_disc">The Mausoleum of Emperor Menelik Ii is located in Addis Ababa.
        The palace, erected in the 18th century, houses the tombs of Menelik II and most of
        Ethiopia is royal family, plus their prized possessions. Explore the Mausoleum of Menelik
        II and be a part of Ethiopia's history. After your tour at the base chambers, join
        the locals in prayer upstairs</string>

    <string name="meskel_disc">Meskel Square (often transliterated as Meskal or Mesqel) is a square
        in the city of Addis Ababa, Ethiopia. It is often a site for public gathering or for
        demonstrations and festivals, notably, the Meskel Festival from which it takes its name.</string>

    <string name="menilik_square_disc">The majestic sculpture of a mounted Emperor Menelik II armed
        with two spears, with the horse facing north towards Adwa, stands proudly in the Square.
        The monument was erected by Emperor Haile Selassie and was dedicated a day before his
        coronation in 1930. On the anniversary of the victory of the Battle of Adwa which occurred
        on St. George’s Day (March 1), the Emperor would lay a wreath at the statue after attending
        mass at St George Cathedral.</string>

    <string name="twedros_disc">Sebastopol was the name of a large artillery mortar commissioned by
        the Ethiopian emperor Tewodros II. The name was taken from the Crimean town Sevastopol, the
        site of a battle during the Crimean War. The mortar weighed approximately 6.7 tons, and was
        capable of firing off half-ton artillery rounds.</string>

    <string name="meyazia_disc">Meyazia 27 Square, commonly known as Arat Kilo, is a square in
        Addis Ababa. In its center is the eponymous monument, commemorating Ethiopia\'s liberation
        from Fascist Italy. In the Ethiopian Calendar Meyazia 27 (May 5), is both the day when
        Addis Ababa fell to Italy in the March of the Iron Will and the day when Emperor Haile
        Selassie triumphantly returned to the city after its liberation.</string>

    <string name="addis_disc">Addis Ababa (Amharic: አዲስ አበባ, Addis Abäba IPA: [adˈdis ˈabəba],
        "new flower"; or Addis Abeba (the spelling used by the official Ethiopian Mapping Authority);
        Odia: Finfinnee, "natural spring"), is the capital and largest city of Ethiopia. It is the
        seat of the Ethiopian federal government. According to the 2007 population census, the city
        has a total population of 2,739,551 inhabitants.</string>
</resources>
